{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946191764","data":{"timestamp":" 946946191764"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946199040","data":{"timestamp":" 946946199040"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946216223","data":{"timestamp":" 946946216222"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 0103e2a8-6786-4dc4-a302-ea783b9b6077"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taji_taji-lele-bibo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taji"," userResponse":" taji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946230017","data":{"timestamp":" 946946230017"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 0103e2a8-6786-4dc4-a302-ea783b9b6077"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_taya-wewe-ruka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" ruka"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946239258","data":{"timestamp":" 946946239258"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 0103e2a8-6786-4dc4-a302-ea783b9b6077"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_taya-wewe-ruka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" taya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946248283","data":{"timestamp":" 946946248283"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 0103e2a8-6786-4dc4-a302-ea783b9b6077"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_mara-ziwa-taya"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" taya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946258290","data":{"timestamp":" 946946258289"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 0103e2a8-6786-4dc4-a302-ea783b9b6077"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tawi_ziwa-tuna-tawi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tawi"," userResponse":" tawi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946272979","data":{"timestamp":" 946946272979"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 0103e2a8-6786-4dc4-a302-ea783b9b6077"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_nini-moja-taya"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" moja"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946293175","data":{"timestamp":" 946946293175"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 0103e2a8-6786-4dc4-a302-ea783b9b6077"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_nini-moja-taya"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" taya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946312858","data":{"timestamp":" 946946312858"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 0103e2a8-6786-4dc4-a302-ea783b9b6077"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_nini-moja-taya"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946530937","data":{"timestamp":" 946946530937"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 6f95f05c-277a-49a4-8bfb-0b40c125482f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_6-9-4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946537162","data":{"timestamp":" 946946537162"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 6f95f05c-277a-49a4-8bfb-0b40c125482f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_7-8-9"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946544631","data":{"timestamp":" 946946544631"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 6f95f05c-277a-49a4-8bfb-0b40c125482f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-7-4"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946545513","data":{"timestamp":" 946946545512"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 6f95f05c-277a-49a4-8bfb-0b40c125482f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-7-4"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946565515","data":{"timestamp":" 946946565515"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 01cc7e57-3c3f-4cb4-92ef-e145bdd638b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taji_taji-lele-bibo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taji"," userResponse":" taji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946577705","data":{"timestamp":" 946946577704"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 01cc7e57-3c3f-4cb4-92ef-e145bdd638b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tawi_tawi-jiji-tele"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tawi"," userResponse":" tawi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946599885","data":{"timestamp":" 946946599885"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 01cc7e57-3c3f-4cb4-92ef-e145bdd638b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_taya-wewe-ruka"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" taya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946617134","data":{"timestamp":" 946946617134"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 01cc7e57-3c3f-4cb4-92ef-e145bdd638b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taka_siri-wivu-taka"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taka"," userResponse":" taka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946635880","data":{"timestamp":" 946946635880"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 01cc7e57-3c3f-4cb4-92ef-e145bdd638b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_nini-moja-taya"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" taya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946648132","data":{"timestamp":" 946946648132"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 01cc7e57-3c3f-4cb4-92ef-e145bdd638b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tawi_ziwa-tuna-tawi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tawi"," userResponse":" tawi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946663205","data":{"timestamp":" 946946663205"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 01cc7e57-3c3f-4cb4-92ef-e145bdd638b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taja_maji-taja-koko"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taja"," userResponse":" taja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946676914","data":{"timestamp":" 946946676914"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 01cc7e57-3c3f-4cb4-92ef-e145bdd638b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taka_taka-ziko-goli"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taka"," userResponse":" taka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946686493","data":{"timestamp":" 946946686492"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 01cc7e57-3c3f-4cb4-92ef-e145bdd638b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_mara-ziwa-taya"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" taya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946702802","data":{"timestamp":" 946946702802"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 01cc7e57-3c3f-4cb4-92ef-e145bdd638b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_ndoo-taya-yeye"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" taya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946708558","data":{"timestamp":" 946946708558"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 01cc7e57-3c3f-4cb4-92ef-e145bdd638b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_ndoo-taya-yeye"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946719307","data":{"timestamp":" 946946719307"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" a04a342f-8dbd-4fde-98cd-8613382593f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946719531","data":{"timestamp":" 946946719531"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" a04a342f-8dbd-4fde-98cd-8613382593f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946720509","data":{"timestamp":" 946946720508"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" a04a342f-8dbd-4fde-98cd-8613382593f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946721781","data":{"timestamp":" 946946721781"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" a04a342f-8dbd-4fde-98cd-8613382593f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946724335","data":{"timestamp":" 946946724335"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" a04a342f-8dbd-4fde-98cd-8613382593f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946724430","data":{"timestamp":" 946946724430"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" a04a342f-8dbd-4fde-98cd-8613382593f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ta.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946739950","data":{"timestamp":" 946946739950"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" aceb7b1c-dfac-41b2-8cf3-ee1309a57234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ta.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_c_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ta.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946757649","data":{"timestamp":" 946946757649"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" aceb7b1c-dfac-41b2-8cf3-ee1309a57234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ta.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ta__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ta.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946763292","data":{"timestamp":" 946946763292"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" aceb7b1c-dfac-41b2-8cf3-ee1309a57234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ta.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ta__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ta.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946772626","data":{"timestamp":" 946946772626"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" aceb7b1c-dfac-41b2-8cf3-ee1309a57234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ta.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ta__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ta.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946786825","data":{"timestamp":" 946946786825"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" aceb7b1c-dfac-41b2-8cf3-ee1309a57234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ta.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ta__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ta.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946789879","data":{"timestamp":" 946946789879"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" aceb7b1c-dfac-41b2-8cf3-ee1309a57234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ta.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ta__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ta.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946801508","data":{"timestamp":" 946946801508"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" aceb7b1c-dfac-41b2-8cf3-ee1309a57234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ta.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ta__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ta.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946805071","data":{"timestamp":" 946946805071"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" aceb7b1c-dfac-41b2-8cf3-ee1309a57234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ta.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ta__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ta.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946813466","data":{"timestamp":" 946946813466"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" aceb7b1c-dfac-41b2-8cf3-ee1309a57234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ta.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ta__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ta.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946831758","data":{"timestamp":" 946946831758"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" aceb7b1c-dfac-41b2-8cf3-ee1309a57234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ta.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ta__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ta.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946848556","data":{"timestamp":" 946946848556"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 566381ed-36dc-41c3-b1bd-4ed24ee45884"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ta.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_c_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ta.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946886702","data":{"timestamp":" 946946886702"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 566381ed-36dc-41c3-b1bd-4ed24ee45884"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ta.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ta__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ta.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946889505","data":{"timestamp":" 946946889505"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 566381ed-36dc-41c3-b1bd-4ed24ee45884"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ta.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ta__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ta.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946899721","data":{"timestamp":" 946946899721"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 566381ed-36dc-41c3-b1bd-4ed24ee45884"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ta.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ta__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ta.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946904025","data":{"timestamp":" 946946904025"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 566381ed-36dc-41c3-b1bd-4ed24ee45884"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ta.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ta__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ta.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946907442","data":{"timestamp":" 946946907442"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 566381ed-36dc-41c3-b1bd-4ed24ee45884"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ta.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ta__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ta.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946915140","data":{"timestamp":" 946946915140"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 566381ed-36dc-41c3-b1bd-4ed24ee45884"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ta.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ta__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ta.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946926464","data":{"timestamp":" 946946926463"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 566381ed-36dc-41c3-b1bd-4ed24ee45884"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ta.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ta__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ta.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946932572","data":{"timestamp":" 946946932572"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 566381ed-36dc-41c3-b1bd-4ed24ee45884"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ta.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ta__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ta.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946941579","data":{"timestamp":" 946946941578"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 566381ed-36dc-41c3-b1bd-4ed24ee45884"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ta.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ta__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ta.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946946101","data":{"timestamp":" 946946946101"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 566381ed-36dc-41c3-b1bd-4ed24ee45884"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ta.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ta__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ta.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946953754","data":{"timestamp":" 946946953754"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 566381ed-36dc-41c3-b1bd-4ed24ee45884"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ta.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ta__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ta.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946956509","data":{"timestamp":" 946946956509"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 566381ed-36dc-41c3-b1bd-4ed24ee45884"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ta.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ta__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ta.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946960941","data":{"timestamp":" 946946960941"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 566381ed-36dc-41c3-b1bd-4ed24ee45884"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ta.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ta__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ta.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946962980","data":{"timestamp":" 946946962980"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 566381ed-36dc-41c3-b1bd-4ed24ee45884"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ta.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ta__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ta.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946972902","data":{"timestamp":" 946946972902"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 566381ed-36dc-41c3-b1bd-4ed24ee45884"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ta.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ta__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ta.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946974609","data":{"timestamp":" 946946974609"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 566381ed-36dc-41c3-b1bd-4ed24ee45884"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ta.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ta__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ta.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946984254","data":{"timestamp":" 946946984254"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 566381ed-36dc-41c3-b1bd-4ed24ee45884"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ta.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ta__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ta.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946988313","data":{"timestamp":" 946946988312"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 566381ed-36dc-41c3-b1bd-4ed24ee45884"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ta.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ta__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ta.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946946992674","data":{"timestamp":" 946946992674"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 566381ed-36dc-41c3-b1bd-4ed24ee45884"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ta.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ta__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ta.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947003015","data":{"timestamp":" 946947003015"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 566381ed-36dc-41c3-b1bd-4ed24ee45884"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ta.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ta__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ta.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947005230","data":{"timestamp":" 946947005230"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 566381ed-36dc-41c3-b1bd-4ed24ee45884"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ta.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ta__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ta.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947006362","data":{"timestamp":" 946947006362"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 566381ed-36dc-41c3-b1bd-4ed24ee45884"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ta.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ta__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951397094","data":{"timestamp":" 946951397093"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 7837d7de-0467-4011-b273-dce54c12305b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_6+1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951407309","data":{"timestamp":" 946951407309"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 7837d7de-0467-4011-b273-dce54c12305b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1+2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951431092","data":{"timestamp":" 946951431092"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 7837d7de-0467-4011-b273-dce54c12305b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_6+1"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951438295","data":{"timestamp":" 946951438295"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 7837d7de-0467-4011-b273-dce54c12305b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_6+1"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951448265","data":{"timestamp":" 946951448264"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 7837d7de-0467-4011-b273-dce54c12305b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1+3"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951454168","data":{"timestamp":" 946951454168"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 7837d7de-0467-4011-b273-dce54c12305b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1+3"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951466530","data":{"timestamp":" 946951466530"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 7837d7de-0467-4011-b273-dce54c12305b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_0+3"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951483626","data":{"timestamp":" 946951483626"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 7837d7de-0467-4011-b273-dce54c12305b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_0+3"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951499642","data":{"timestamp":" 946951499642"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 7837d7de-0467-4011-b273-dce54c12305b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_5+1"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951502087","data":{"timestamp":" 946951502086"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 7837d7de-0467-4011-b273-dce54c12305b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_5+1"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951510131","data":{"timestamp":" 946951510131"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 7837d7de-0467-4011-b273-dce54c12305b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_5+1"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951530442","data":{"timestamp":" 946951530442"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 7837d7de-0467-4011-b273-dce54c12305b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1+4"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951532567","data":{"timestamp":" 946951532567"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 7837d7de-0467-4011-b273-dce54c12305b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1+4"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951536300","data":{"timestamp":" 946951536300"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 7837d7de-0467-4011-b273-dce54c12305b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1+4"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951537777","data":{"timestamp":" 946951537776"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 7837d7de-0467-4011-b273-dce54c12305b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_1+4"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951563799","data":{"timestamp":" 946951563798"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 22fd4e08-da5f-4587-80d4-c3d77bdd1c67"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wako_kwao-wako-hivi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wako"," userResponse":" kwao"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951577680","data":{"timestamp":" 946951577680"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 22fd4e08-da5f-4587-80d4-c3d77bdd1c67"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wako_kwao-wako-hivi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wako"," userResponse":" wako"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951587478","data":{"timestamp":" 946951587478"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 22fd4e08-da5f-4587-80d4-c3d77bdd1c67"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_waje_humu-waje-njia"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" waje"," userResponse":" waje"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951644305","data":{"timestamp":" 946951644305"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 335f436d-2143-46cb-ac51-0256319b48c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_waje_humu-waje-njia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" waje"," userResponse":" waje"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951653372","data":{"timestamp":" 946951653372"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 335f436d-2143-46cb-ac51-0256319b48c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wana_yenu-wana-wewe"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wana"," userResponse":" wana"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951670155","data":{"timestamp":" 946951670155"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 335f436d-2143-46cb-ac51-0256319b48c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wake_wake-yawe-pale"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wake"," userResponse":" wake"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951689049","data":{"timestamp":" 946951689049"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 335f436d-2143-46cb-ac51-0256319b48c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wako_isha-moto-wako"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wako"," userResponse":" wako"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951697649","data":{"timestamp":" 946951697649"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 335f436d-2143-46cb-ac51-0256319b48c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wale_wale-papa-zile"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wale"," userResponse":" wale"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951708654","data":{"timestamp":" 946951708654"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 335f436d-2143-46cb-ac51-0256319b48c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_waje_hiki-humo-waje"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" waje"," userResponse":" humo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951711673","data":{"timestamp":" 946951711672"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 335f436d-2143-46cb-ac51-0256319b48c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_waje_hiki-humo-waje"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951720667","data":{"timestamp":" 946951720667"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 9579a947-654d-4c9f-bffd-cb4b97834983"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951720892","data":{"timestamp":" 946951720891"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 9579a947-654d-4c9f-bffd-cb4b97834983"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951721865","data":{"timestamp":" 946951721865"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 9579a947-654d-4c9f-bffd-cb4b97834983"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951723139","data":{"timestamp":" 946951723139"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 9579a947-654d-4c9f-bffd-cb4b97834983"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951726040","data":{"timestamp":" 946951726040"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 9579a947-654d-4c9f-bffd-cb4b97834983"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951726892","data":{"timestamp":" 946951726892"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 9579a947-654d-4c9f-bffd-cb4b97834983"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951727210","data":{"timestamp":" 946951727210"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 9579a947-654d-4c9f-bffd-cb4b97834983"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951728449","data":{"timestamp":" 946951728449"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 9579a947-654d-4c9f-bffd-cb4b97834983"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951731977","data":{"timestamp":" 946951731976"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 9579a947-654d-4c9f-bffd-cb4b97834983"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951732971","data":{"timestamp":" 946951732970"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 9579a947-654d-4c9f-bffd-cb4b97834983"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951733228","data":{"timestamp":" 946951733228"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 9579a947-654d-4c9f-bffd-cb4b97834983"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951734186","data":{"timestamp":" 946951734186"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 9579a947-654d-4c9f-bffd-cb4b97834983"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951737041","data":{"timestamp":" 946951737041"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 9579a947-654d-4c9f-bffd-cb4b97834983"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951738075","data":{"timestamp":" 946951738075"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 9579a947-654d-4c9f-bffd-cb4b97834983"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951738554","data":{"timestamp":" 946951738554"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 9579a947-654d-4c9f-bffd-cb4b97834983"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951743058","data":{"timestamp":" 946951743058"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 9579a947-654d-4c9f-bffd-cb4b97834983"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951743197","data":{"timestamp":" 946951743197"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_033618"," gameId":" 9579a947-654d-4c9f-bffd-cb4b97834983"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}